takimag.com 2019-11-28

# Taki's Magazine - Privacy Policy - Taki's Magazine

At Takimag.com we appreciate your readership and value your personal privacy. We respect the personal nature of the information you provide us on our web site and acknowledge the importance of protecting this information. [In adopting this privacy policy, our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using your personal information with your reasonable expectations of privacy]. The policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our policy.

At Takimag.com we collect different types of information about our users in three main contexts: (1) when you share your e-mail address or subscribe to email newsletters or request site updates, (2) when you share personal information while providing tips to our editors, (3) when you share personal information while posting comments on our posts or stories. We may also ask for other information at other times but at no time will you be required to share any personal information to gain complete access to our site. In addition to personal information — such as name, street and e-mail addresses, and telephone numbers — we may also collect information that is in no way personally identifiable. This may include the operating system you are working on, the internet browser you are using, the domain name of your internet service provider, and the web sites you visit directly before and after your visit to Takimag.com.

The more we know about you, the better we are able to customize our web site to suit your personal preferences and interests. The e-mail address you provide may be used by Takimag.com for any reason, such as contacting you for editorial purposes or to advise you of any changes to our site. We may also from time to time send you messages about our marketing partners’ products.

To maintain a site that is free of charge and does not require registration, we display advertisements on our web site. We also use the information you give us to help our advertisers target the audience they want to reach. At no time does any party other than Takimag.com have access to your personally identifiable information, and you will never be contacted by any party other than Takimag.com unless you have requested to be so contacted. The only exceptions to the foregoing are that we may disclose personally identifiable information (i) in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order, (ii) in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take actions regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of another person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law, or (iii) in the event we are acquired by or merged with another company.

When you sign up for our updates or receive e-mail messages from Takimag.com, you will always be given the chance to opt-out of special offers and site updates. You may change your preferences at any time and will only be contacted in manners consistent with your stated preferences.  
Non-personally identifiable information (such as stated above) may be shared in aggregate form with our advertisers or marketing partners but your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed to them.

Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an advertisement (but not your name, address, or other personal information), may be used to serve advertisements to you on this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, third party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

Third parties and web sites that have links on our site may also collect or use information about you. This privacy statement does not cover the information practices of other companies or people that Takimag.com does not employ or manage.

Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments pages or in any forums we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk. Privacy is a very personal matter and we encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.

Our site is accessible via the Internet and so may potentially be accessed by anyone around the world. Other users may access the site from outside the United States. This means that, where you choose to post your data on the site, this could be accessed from anywhere around the world and therefore a transfer of your data outside of the U.S. may be deemed to have occurred. You consent to such transfer of your data for and by way of this purpose. Where we or our contractors transfer data outside of the U.S. this is only ever done with the relevant protections required by law in place.
